Chapter 1 Memories of a Pill Sovereign

“Who am I? I am… Long Chen!”

“I look down on the very heavens, the arrogant nine heavens’ peerless Pill Sovereign - Long Chen? ...I am someone who is cheated and bullied by everyone, a spineless, good-for-nothing cripple incapable of cultivating - Long Chen?”

His mind was a whirl of confusion, and at the same time, severe pain came from all over his body. Long Chen was unable to stop his mind’s chaotic thoughts and emitted a pained groan.

“Chen-er, you’ve finally awakened? Thank god, your mom was worried sick about you! If you want to brag about how strong you are, then fine, but why did you have to go duel with those people!?”

A kind and gentle voice sounded beside Long Chen’s ear. That voice was full of happiness and comfort, but toward the end, it also became choked with emotion.

Long Chen slowly opened his eyes. His blurry vision gradually became clearer, and a woman’s face appeared before him.

The woman appeared to be in her thirties and she was extremely beautiful. However, at the corner of her eyes were some deep wrinkles that did not match up with her young age.

Currently, this woman was tearfully looking at Long Chen with eyes that were full of love, making Long Chen’s heart feel a burst of warmth.

“Child, you scared your mom to death.” As the woman spoke, her eyes became even redder and her tears streamed down.

“Mom???”

Long Chen looked at this familiar yet strange face. He doubtingly said this one word, his face filled with confusion.

“Child, don’t scare your mom! Don’t you recognize me?” The woman’s face immediately became panicked.

At this moment, an elderly man appeared beside the woman. He examined Long Chen and he said, “Mrs. Long, Long Chen suffered a blow to the back of his head so it’s possible he will need to rest a bit to recover his memories. Don’t be too worried; just now I gave the young master some medicine. The medicinal energy still hasn’t completely dissolved, so just let the young master rest for a bit longer.”

Mrs. Long worriedly looked at Long Chen. Reluctantly, she nodded her head and followed the elderly man out of the room.

Long Chen heard the elderly man advising the woman softly in the distance, “Mrs. Long, the fact that young master Long managed to return with his life is already infinitely lucky. Don’t force it too much.”

Mrs. Long tremblingly replied, “Master alchemist’s meaning is that my son will…”

The elderly man, who had been called an alchemist, sighed, “The young master’s hindbrain received an acute shock. To tell the truth, being able to wake up is already extremely lucky; however, the repercussions will definitely still be very severe. Losing his memory is quite possible in this situation…”

The two people gradually walked further and further away so Long Chen could no longer hear them clearly... But what was barely audible to him was the sound of Mrs. Long’s sobbing.

Long Chen gazed blankly at the ceiling above as he felt the severe pains throughout his body, especially at the back of his head which was bursting with swollen, aching pain.

Just what happened? I’m Long Chen, and so Mrs. Long is my flesh and blood mother. How could I have such an unfamiliar feeling?

And all these confusing memories, where did they come from? I have memories that I’m an arrogant, exceedingly powerful person… but at the same time, I remember that I’m an often bullied and extorted bitter trash?

Pill Sovereign Long Chen? Trash Long Chen? Which is the real me? Am I the Pill Sovereign’s reincarnation? Or am I a fusion of the Pill Sovereign’s soul with a trash weakling?

Long Chen’s mind was full of endless questions. “Whatever, it doesn’t matter. I am Long Chen. Whether I’m Pill Sovereign Long Chen or the old, crippled Long Chen doesn’t mean anything right now. The most important thing is that I’m still alive.

“I have two sets of memories that have mixed together; how would I even try to fix this kind of insane problem? Instead, what I need to do now is to let myself recover as quickly as possible.”

Sensing his body’s current condition, he quickly located many fractures. He had three broken ribs, one arm broken in two places, and most severe of all, his hindbrain was injured to the point where a large portion of his scalp had caved in. He had definitely been the victim of an extremely vicious assault.

“Huh, although I have no way to condense energy, my Spiritual Strength appears to be extremely powerful. I can actually sense everything within thirty meters of my body.”

Long Chen was pleasantly surprised. According to his garbled memories, Spiritual Strength was invaluable, especially to pill cultivators!

Profit, profit! Whether he was the reincarnation of a Pill Sovereign or his soul was just a mix containing the Pill Sovereign’s memories, the present him had definitely profited greatly.

The Pill Sovereign had lived an entire lifetime already, and now that allowed him to possess an exceptionally strong soul; just what kind of awesomeness was this?

However, when he carefully examined his body, his expression changed. “My Spiritual Root has been taken away. My abdomen’s Spirit Bone is also missing a piece that appears to be dug out. And my heart has a hole? Just who would be this ruthless and take my Spirit Root, Spirit Bone and Spirit Blood? No wonder I can’t cultivate!” Long Chen was completely infuriated.

His current Spiritual Strength was much, much stronger than his old self. It was now strong enough for him to immediately figure out the mystery of why he was a cripple who couldn’t cultivate.

The Spirit Root was located in the Dantian; it was the foundation for all cultivators. Without the Spirit Root, there was no way to sense heaven and earth’s spiritual energy, let alone absorb it for cultivating.

Spirit Blood was something that people were born with; it was a trace of blood that gave you innate talent. While basically all people were born with it, the majority of cultivators didn’t know anything about it.

The Spirit Bone was found in the pit of a person’s abdomen and slightly bulged out. Ordinary people wouldn’t have a Spirit Bone. Even amongst cultivators, maybe only one in ten thousand would have one, which marked them as a genius.

However, Long Chen’s Spirit Bone was obviously missing a piece and had clear marks of being dug out by someone.

His face became exceedingly unsightly. If his memories were not all mixed up, then how could he not remember who had done this to his body?

Although these three things were precious to him, they wouldn’t have any use once they left his body. If they wanted to harm him, why did they have to use such a harsh method? Using this kind of method was practically causing him to live a life worse than death!

However, anger only brought on more anger, and since he was already missing them, being angry did not have any use.

You better not let me find out who did this.

Long Chen couldn’t help but gnash his teeth in anger. This was an extremely great blow to him. With him possessing a Spirit Bone, even if he had been an idiot, he would still have been an absolute genius.

But now some despicable bastard had caused him to become a useless person who was incapable of cultivating, causing him to be humiliated and receive condescending looks from practically everyone.

Just when Long Chen was about to furiously erupt, the door of the room was gently pushed open, and a pretty thirteen-year-old maiden walked in. This was Long Chen’s maid who was called Bao-er.

“Young master, it’s time to take some medicine.”

“Medicine? What medicine is it?” Long Chen’s nose sniffed slightly as he asked.

“This is something Mrs. Long paid an enormous price for. It’s a Tiger Bone Pill that can quickly heal young master’s injuries,” Bao-er replied.

She opened the small, elaborate case in her hand, revealing the medicinal pill inside. “It is said that this medicinal pill came from grandmaster Yun Qi. The medicinal strength is very strong.”

Looking at the thing, Long Chen’s face became a bit strange. Even this kind of plaything could be called a pill? Its shape was extremely uneven and seemed more like a meatball.

Even not talking about the shape, its color was completely black and there wasn’t even a trace of luster. If it wasn’t emitting a very faint medicinal aroma, then Long Chen might even suspect that it was a ball of sheep dung.

After staring at the thing in his hand for a long time, Long Chen finally sighed. Someone who had ended up losing over eighty percent of the medicinal pill’s essence could still be called a grandmaster? Long Chen bewilderedly wondered how someone could have created something so soft and mushy.

Pills could be divided into five grades: low grade, middle grade, high grade, top grade, and peerless grade. As for the pill in his hand, it couldn’t even count as one of the five grades. Long Chen suddenly realized that this was just a defective good. It was a trash pill. Normally, alchemists would definitely not sell this kind of medicinal pills since they couldn’t afford to lose their customers. Oftentimes, they would be turned into medicinal liquids or just directly thrown out.

“Young master, don’t daydream. In order to obtain this precious pill, Mrs. Long already sold off her own precious jewelry. You should hurry and take it,” urged Bao-er.

Long Chen couldn’t help but feel some pain in his heart. His impression of his mother was that she loved him very dearly to the point where it was like he was drowning in love. It had reached the point where his mother would basically never refuse any of his requests.

His mother had done everything and anything for him. She had given birth to him while she was still young. She had been gifted with great beauty growing up, but now she was barely thirty-something years old and already had wrinkles in the corners of her eyes. Seeing those deep wrinkles, Long Chen knew that she had already sacrificed far too much for him.

Looking at the medicinal pill in his hand, he observed that even though it was a defective good, at least the medicinal ingredients inside it were not bad. Impurities took up over eighty percent of it, but it wouldn’t have any problems healing his injuries.

Taking the medicinal pill, Long Chen ordered Bao-er to not leak any news of him out, except to his mother of course.

Although Bao-er didn’t really understand why, she still trusted Long Chen and obediently nodded.

After taking the medicine, although Long Chen had no way to use cultivation to absorb the medicinal strength, he managed to guide the medicinal energy to his wounds by using his formidable Spiritual Strength, allowing him to recover extremely quickly.

The second day, Long Chen slowly opened his eyes. He had a smile plastered on his mouth as he exercised his muscles.

“Excellent! Although that medicine was pretty bad, the medicinal ingredients themselves were of high quality. Other than my hindbrain, the majority of my injuries have already healed, and the amount of energy left is more than enough to heal me completely.”

He slowly walked toward the mirror. Looking at his reflection, he saw a nothing-out-of-the-ordinary, handsome youngster with eyebrows like swords and bright eyes. Long Chen took a deep breath. “From today onward, I, Long Chen, will no longer be the previous Long Chen. I will rise above others.”

Although his body was still slightly weak, walking was no longer a problem. Long Chen left the room and saw that the sun had already risen in the east.

After pondering deeply for an hour, he called over Bao-er and gave her a list of medicinal ingredients to go find.

However, Bao-er’s expression became a bit embarrassed. Long Chen wondered what it was before quickly remembering that the current Long family was extremely hard-pressed for money, and Bao-er had no method to get a loan.

Otherwise, his mother would not have had to sell off her own jewelry, a part of her exceptionally precious dowry. The present Long family had already fallen into extremely dire straits.

Feeling around in his pocket, he found slightly over eighty silver coins. Although this wasn’t a lot, it was enough to buy the medicinal ingredients on his list.

Bao-er worked diligently, and not even two hours later, she had managed to buy the medicinal ingredients. Long Chen immediately set about measuring and dividing them into different portions before boiling them in a large bowl.

Six hours later, a very thick medicinal liquid was releasing a medicinal aroma. As Long Chen looked into the bowl of cheap medicinal liquid, a smile appeared on his face.

“I, Long Chen, will rise above others, starting from this one bowl of medicinal liquid.”

Chapter 2 Despicable Scum

The medicinal liquid entered his stomach, and Long Chen hastily used his mind to guide the medicinal energy throughout his body, allowing it to merge into his bones.

Normal martial artists would let the medicinal energy assimilate inside the Dantian in order to absorb it, and only later would they spread it throughout their bodies. However, Long Chen didn’t have a Spirit Root; thus, his Dantian was completely empty and had no way to store energy.

The only thing he could do was to allow the medicinal energy to scatter into every cell. Although this medicinal liquid was formed only from ordinary medicinal herbs, it displayed a surprisingly remarkable medicinal effect after going through Long Chen’s pairings and proportions.

As the medicinal energy rushed throughout his body, countless pores opened up. It was as if every single cell had been in a state of starvation as they all began to crazily absorb the spiritual energy of heaven and earth.

BOOM!

A muffled explosion came from within Long Chen’s body. His originally sealed meridians were all forced open and Long Chen couldn’t stop himself from letting out a muffled groan.

When others cultivated, they would use the Dantian’s qi in order to gradually open up their meridians in a step-by-step manner which would not cause any pain.

However, Long Chen couldn’t do so; he could only borrow an external energy source. This energy was like the ocean’s water flowing into a river field; its violent and ferocious nature wasn’t something that just anybody could withstand.

“This pain… I will definitely remember this pain.” Long Chen gnashed his teeth. If it weren’t for some vicious person stealing his Spirit Root, how could he have been forced to choose such a crazy method?

BANG BANG BANG!

Continuous explosions echoed out from his body as his meridians opened up one by one. Every time a meridian channel was opened, intense pain would wrack his body.

When all his meridians were finally opened, Long Chen almost fell into a coma. He had to rest for two full hours before he slowly revitalized himself.

With the pain now past him, Long Chen felt that the pores from his toes to his head were all open. With every single breath he took, he absorbed the spiritual energy of heaven and earth.

“Excellent, I can finally practice cultivation now that my meridians have opened.”

Long Chen sensed his body’s condition. With his meridians opened, he could finally absorb spiritual qi from the world through his pores in order to nourish his body to become stronger.

In fact, although his meridians had only just been opened, that single change filled his body with strength.

He punched out, and the whistling wind that came with it made Long Chen smile. He hadn’t endured that pain for nothing.

For ordinary cultivators, they first had to enter a so-called qi sensing realm. Only once they were able to sense qi could they enter the Qi Condensation realm.

However, Long Chen had taken an alternative path. By using medicinal energy to forcibly link himself up to heaven and earth’s spiritual qi, he had managed to completely open his meridians, which was equivalent to stepping into Qi Condensation with a single step.

However, it couldn’t be said that he had truly stepped into Qi Condensation. Although his body had been strengthened to the point that it was on that level, the Qi Condensation realm involved condensing cyclones of qi within the Dantian. Without a Dantian, he was not truly in Qi Condensation.

“Although I’ve forcibly opened my meridians, my useless Dantian is still unable to hold the true qi. When I fight with others, there’s no way I can keep it up for more than a few moments. This still isn’t good enough.”

Long Chen went through his new memories. Almost all of his new memories were only about alchemy. But eventually, he found the only memory he had that pertained to martial arts: the Nine Star Hegemon Body Art.

What surprised Long Chen pleasantly was that the Nine Star Hegemon Body Art was practically custom-made for him. It was a secret technique capable of excavating even more of a person’s potential. It didn’t cultivate the Dantian, but the nine stars.

Those nine stars were contained within the body. Once they were all formed, they would be equivalent to nine Dantians. When he saw that in his memories, he almost jumped in joy.

But then as he continued comprehending this technique, he immediately felt as if a bucket of ice water had been thrown over him. To cultivate the Nine Star Hegemon Body Art required countless medicinal pills.

In order to condense the first star, the FengFu Star, he would practically need an endless amount of energy. If he wanted to rely on just absorbing the energy from the air, not even a hundred years would be enough to condense it.

In order to condense the first star, he would need an enormous number of medicinal pills. Without them, he wouldn’t be able to cultivate in it.

His Long family was broke, and there was no way for them to purchase such a huge number of medicinal pills.

“I should first think of a method to make some money,” Long Chen muttered to himself. After changing his clothes, he left his room. At this time, it was already past noon, but there were unexpectedly few people to be seen in his huge noble estate, making it seem like an extremely desolate place.

Long Chen’s father was the Border Suppression Marquis. He was currently away at the barbarian border. Long Chen and his mother had had to suffer many condescending gazes from everyone in the imperial capital over the past few years. Although they had the position of a noble family, compared to before, they were completely destitute. In their entire estate, there were only ten or so maids who did some part-time work for them since they couldn’t afford to employ more people.

It could be said that in all the aristocracy, they were the family in the worst straits, and Long Chen himself was the most destitute of the poor.

Phoenix Cry Empire was currently in a golden age of martial arts. Basically, everyone practiced martial arts. But as it had turned out, Long Chen’s trash physique meant that he was incapable of practicing martial arts, making him someone that everybody would sneer at.

Opposite to Long Chen was his father, Long Tianxiao. He was the strongest of his generation and with him guarding the barbarian border, even if the barbarian tribes were to savagely attack, they would not have the ability to step even half a foot into the Phoenix Cry Empire.

Long Tianxiao was the Phoenix Cry Empire’s military god of this generation, whereas Long Chen had been trash that couldn’t even sense qi. It was impossible to prevent people from feeling that this tiger father had had a dog of a son.

Countless people would jeer at him, but Long Chen wouldn’t care. However, that day, the Savage Marquis’s son, Zhou Yaoyang, had ridiculed Long Chen by saying that he wasn’t his father’s son.

Long Chen’s anger had immediately soared to the heavens. Zhou Yaoyang had obviously been insulting his mother as unfaithful! Long Chen’s anger had even caused him to become muddle-headed and he had recklessly challenged his opponent to a duel.

However, his opponent was a strong person at the seventh Heavenstage of Qi Condensation while he was just an ordinary person incapable of even sensing qi. He had basically been asking to be disgraced.

As a result, he was later beaten to the point of losing consciousness and almost dying. He was sent home and the news caused Long Chen to be an object of ridicule for quite some time in the imperial capital.

Leaving his noble estate, Long Chen went directly to the imperial capital’s Hundred Herb Market. That was the place where all kinds of precious medicinal ingredients were sold. Right now, what he needed to do was to get an understanding of the medicinal herbs’ market situation.

Along the road, there were quite a few people and when they recognized Long Chen, they couldn’t help but point at him behind his back; however, Long Chen was already used to this.

But at the same time, he smiled bitterly inside. His own father had suppressed the entire barbarian border, which was an amazing, meritorious deed that protected the entire empire.

However, what had he obtained for that? This mother and son duo had been left to suffer from bullying and humiliating stares in the imperial capital, and Long Chen had almost been beaten to death. How could this be considered repayment? A group of people that were protected by his father had all given his son condescending gazes. Was this his repayment?

Long Chen quickened his footsteps. Although he wasn’t afraid of this kind of stares, he would always end up a bit gloomy. But at this moment, his path was suddenly blocked by a group of people.

“Aiya, are you actually Long Chen? I heard you were beaten to the point where you couldn’t even recognize your own mom, so how are you so lively that you ran out today?”

In front of Long Chen was a sixteen-year-old teen wearing gaudy clothes and sneering at him with two guards.

This person was also born as a noble heir in an aristocrat family and was called Li Hao. However, his position within the aristocracy was not high and his status was incomparable to Long Chen’s. After all, in the Phoenix Cry Empire, nobility and status were only secondary as strength was still the most important thing.

Li Hao was standing right in the middle of the road and if Long Chen wanted to go through, he would need to pass through him.

If it was the previous Long Chen, he would have turned around and walked back, but today’s Long Chen looked at Li Hao, shook his head, and sighed, “People say even well-trained dogs know not to obstruct the road. Looks like you’re not even as good as a dog.”

“Long Chen, it seems you don’t remember the lesson that I gave you last time! If you want to be beaten within an inch of your life again, then let’s fight in the martial arena.” Li Hao’s expression changed before taunting him once again.

“That’s why I said you were a dog. Just go eat crap with Zhou Yaoyang.” Long Chen shook his head. He didn’t want to waste his time on this kind of person. He needed to handle his own affairs, so he started to walk around him.

“Long Chen, you are asking for it!”

Li Hao couldn’t help but become angry. He was not expecting that the always cowardly Long Chen would actually act in such an unyielding manner that basically didn’t even pay attention to him. He stuck out his arms to bar Long Chen’s path.

Long Chen frowned slightly, but just as he was about to say more, a person walked over and cursed Li Hao, “Li Hao, you’re the one asking for it! Just who do you think you are to dare threaten my brother?”

The person who had come was an extremely tall eighteen-year-old guy. His height was especially extraordinary at seven feet, which was taller than either of them by over a head. He looked very intimidating.

“Shi Feng, this isn’t your business! It’d be best if you didn’t meddle in it.”

When Li Hao saw Shi Feng, all he could do was act tough even though he was weaker. Shi Feng was also a noble heir whose status was about the same as his, but Shi Feng was a strong person who had reached the eighth Heavenstage of Qi Condensation while he was only at the third Heavenstage of Qi Condensation.

In addition, Shi Feng had an innate strength, which meant that amongst people in the same rank as him, only a few were an equal match for him. Therefore, Li Hao didn’t have the guts to challenge Shi Feng.

“Brother Long Chen, I heard that that bastard Zhou Yaoyang beat you up. How about I help you vent your anger? “ Shi Feng looked at Long Chen and his expression became indignant.

Long Chen looked at the huge person in front of him, and his heart felt a bit of warmth. Shi Feng was the only one in the imperial capital who would consider him as his brother.

“No thanks, my enmities are something that I will pay back myself. Just don’t worry about it.” Long Chen faintly laughed, patting Shi Feng’s shoulder.

When Shi Feng heard Long Chen say this, he thought that Long Chen might be worried about his image and so he didn’t raise the issue again.

“Let’s go, come with me for a stroll,” said Long Chen with a smile, and he brought Shi Feng for a walk.

When Li Hao saw that the two of them considered him as just thin air, he couldn’t help but angrily curse, “Long Chen, you little bastard, if you have the guts then you’ll fight me in a duel!”

They had just walked a couple of steps when Li Hao said this and they paused. From deep within Long Chen’s eyes, a strong murderous intent was radiated as he slowly turned his head.

“You want to have a duel with me?” Long Chen’s voice was extremely cold. Each word he spoke was just like ice shards that caused people to tremble in their bones.

Li Hao couldn’t help but shiver. For some reason, he felt that today’s Long Chen was a bit different, but his big words had already been spoken so if he was to act like a coward, then he would become the entire imperial capital’s laughingstock.

Moreover, he was already used to bullying Long Chen over and over, so with those experiences, he ignored the trace of fear that arose in his heart.

“Not bad, you dare to accept the duel?” Li Hao mocked in a loud voice.

“Not a problem, however, I want to add some stakes,” said Long Chen after a moment’s thought.

“Adding stakes? Haha, your Long family is almost unable to feed yourselves, what are you going to take out as stakes? You could use your family’s estate, or how about you become my slave?” mocked Li Hao coldly.

However, what he didn’t notice was that in the corner of Long Chen’s mouth was a callous smile that seemed to have some hidden intentions.

“Brother Shi, can you lend me your martial sword?” Long Chen asked.

“Take it.”

Shi Feng did somewhat hate to part with it, but he still handed his sword over.

Long Chen nodded and he quietly recorded this favor into his heart. Towards Li Hao, he said, “This martial sword isn’t top quality, but it is still worth eight thousand gold coins. For today, I’ll just count it as five thousand gold coins. If you win you can take the martial sword, but if you lose, you have to give me five thousand gold coins. How’s that sound?”

Li Hao’s heart shook; Shi Feng’s sword was made from top quality steel and was forged by a master. It was definitely worth at least eight thousand gold coins.

Today, this idiot Long Chen actually decided to use such a thing as a bet; Li Hao had long since started laughing cheerfully inside.

He once again sneered, “I don’t know. If someone were to lose, will he renege out of the bet?”

“Don’t worry. I, Shi Feng, will guarantee it.” Shi Feng coldly smiled.

“Good, then let’s go to the martial arena to sign the contract. If today I don’t beat the teeth out of you, then in the future I won’t be Li Hao.” Li Hao couldn’t help being extremely exuberant as he spoke high-spiritedly.

Long Chen’s face was still calm; however, within his eyes appeared some darkness. Li Hao was just one of Zhou Yaoyang’s dogs, so Long Chen never paid any attention to him. But nowadays, they were always plotting against him; just what kind of hidden conspiracy was there?

However, no matter what kind of conspiracy it was, the truth would always come to light one day. Long Chen walked directly to the martial arena outside the imperial capital.

Chapter 3 Revealing his Sharp Side

In the Phoenix Cry Empire, martial customs were very popular, and so some disputes were unavoidable. Thus, a life and death stage had been built outside the imperial capital where people could resolve their personal differences.

As long as both parties agreed and signed the martial arena contract, then once they entered the martial arena, even if they killed their opponent, they wouldn’t receive any punishment from the imperial capital.

During most days, this place was filled with bustling crowds, and today was no different. However, after a couple matches had ended, two youngsters walked onto the stage and caused an uproar.

“Isn’t that person Long Chen? Why would he come here?”

“Yeah, yesterday he was almost beaten to death. Isn’t it weird for him to be here today?”

“Hmph, I bet he doesn’t want to live anymore and wants to get someone to beat him to death here.”

His father Long Tianxiao might be called the Border Suppression Marquis and was this generation’s military god, but the people who gave him the title ‘military god’ were the poor people who had to suffer through wars and conflicts.

In the imperial capital, which was filled with rich people, everyone was living in peace and prosperity; therefore, people didn’t place Long Tianxiao, who was born in a commoner family, on the same level as them. And thus, only a few people in the entire imperial capital held respect for Long Chen.

“Long Chen, you piece of trash, why did you come back? Aren’t you just holding up the action for no reason? Who would want to see your martial arts? Hurry up and beat it!”

“Yeah, if you want to kill yourself then find somewhere without people. No one wants to see such a piece of trash, so stop wasting our time!”

In just a moment, the audience of several hundred people were all cursing loudly; none of them hid their disgust for Long Chen.

However, in an unremarkable corner further away, two maidens wearing veils were raptly watching him.

“Sister, that one is your fiancé? Why does he seem so lacking? There are not even the slightest fluctuations around his body,” observed one of the maidens disappointedly.

“Hmph, if dad hadn’t been so selfish, he wouldn’t have arranged my marriage back when I still wasn’t even born. It’s truly irritating…” responded the other maiden.

On the martial arena, Long Chen didn’t even notice the two maidens who were spying on him, and he also did not respond at all to the jeers of the crowd. He merely indifferently looked at Li Hao.

Li Hao pointed out the people’s uproar and sneered. “See? You’re an unwelcome piece of trash, and if you were smart, you would just bash your head in and die.”

Long Chen continued to only indifferently stare at him, not saying a word.

Dong….

The sound of a bell rang out, signaling the start of the duel. When that bell tolled, life and death were separated by a fine line.

Due to the tolling of the bell, the originally rowdy crowd became silent; after all, it was a life and death battle. Who would know just when someone’s life would end?

“Sister, this fiancé of yours doesn’t seem to have any cultivation base while his opponent is at the third Heavenstage of Qi Condensation. Aren’t you worried?” The maiden asked.

“Hmph, what’s the point of me being worried? Him dying is fine. It doesn’t have anything to do with me.” The other maiden indifferently snorted. But although she said these words, she had already taken out an extremely strange and ancient silk net.

“Heehee, don’t say you don’t care, you’ve already taken out your martial weapon. Looks like you do still care. And you know, although his cultivation talent is trash, he’s not that bad looking. How about this, if you don’t want him, you can just give him to me.” the other maiden laughingly joked.

“How can a person be just randomly given to you? If you like him, you can wait for me to withdraw from the marriage arrangement. After that, you can do whatever you want,” responded the other woman angrily.

“Heehee.”

On the martial arena, Long Chen from the beginning until the end had remained as calm as water. When compared to yesterday’s him who had been gnashing his teeth in complete anger, it was as if he was a completely different person.

“Long Chen, with your death near, you decided to suddenly become calm? Don’t worry, due to the stakes you proposed, I won’t beat you to death today.” Li Hao was extremely arrogant and confident.

“You sure say a lot of crap. Hurry up and come at me, I still have things to do,” responded Long Chen in a slightly impatient manner.

Because the entire audience was very quiet, every single word of Long Chen’s managed to enter the crowd’s ears, and in a split second everyone watching the martial arena burst into jeering derision.

“Li Hao, what are you still waiting for? Hurry up and beat this kid to death! He’s really causing us to feel too embarrassed for him.”

Some of the people present recognized Li Hao, so they called out to him.

A cold sneer appeared on Li Hao’s face, and he was no longer hesitating; the power of his third Heavenstage of Qi Condensation completely exploded out. His foot pressed down slightly on the martial arena, and he immediately shot out towards Long Chen, punching out with his fist.

When Li Hao started attacking, the crowd below burst into cheers; the current Li Hao’s appearance appeared very dashing and handsome.

“Nice attack, it’s the Wind Jade Tree Fist.”

Some of the people recognized the move and cheered. However, the distant two maidens’ expressions were both filled with contempt and ridicule.

Long Chen similarly also sneered. This kind of idiot move—filled with mistakes—could still be used against enemies?

The fist was smashing towards him and a strong wind whistled as it approached, but Long Chen seemed to not notice it at all and didn’t move even an inch.

“Haha, this trash doesn’t even know how to dodge,” sneered some people under the stage.

However, just when that ridicule had just been shouted out, Li Hao’s fist came to a complete stop just an inch away from Long Chen’s face.

The originally ridiculing crowd suddenly came to complete silence. They noticed that one of Long Chen’s legs had struck out and violently kicked Li Hao in the area between his legs.

The originally beaming with happiness and elegant Li Hao now had an expression like a purple eggplant. Long Chen’s kick clearly caused him an extremely severe pain, making his facial features warp and preventing him from moving.

However, he might not be able to move from the pain, but Long Chen could. In just this brief pause, Long Chen grabbed Li Hao’s hair, forcefully pulling on it while also strongly kicking out with his knee.

SLAM SLAM SLAM!

Long Chen completed his actions in an extremely refreshing manner and in a short time, his strong and fast rhythmic actions gave people a very intense show.

The unpleasant sound of bones breaking came out from Li Hao’s body. His nose was already caved in, his whole face was covered in blood, and he himself had already lost consciousness.

For a moment, not even one voice could be heard from the crowd. Nobody had expected that a strong person at the third Heavenstage of Qi Condensation would be beaten by trash, who had no cultivation base, in such a quick manner.

Moreover, he had done it in the cleanest and most efficient manner. This kind of result was a firm slap in the face towards the crowd that had been ridiculing him.

Even the distant two observing maidens were completely shocked. Li Hao was nothing to them and could be easily killed with a wave of their hands…

But Long Chen was not the same as them. From the very start, not a trace of spiritual energy had been used by Long Chen and he had completely relied on an ordinary person’s abilities to defeat Li Hao.

“Long Chen wins.”

A voice came from an elderly man below the stage who was often in charge of the martial arena and its registration.

Long Chen’s stomach fluctuated rapidly a couple of times, and it was only with great willpower that he managed to stop and suppress the killing intent inside him. Right now was not the time for killing people.

He had been oppressed for such a long time, and now that he had exploded out, it was hard for him to withdraw it. But as the rest of the world saw it, Long Chen’s actions appeared to be from lack of strength like he was gasping for breath.

Long Chen walked off the stage to the elderly man and received the sword that he had used as his stakes as well as a crystal card with five thousand gold coins on it.

The rules here stated that they had to hand in the stakes to the referee before the match; in order to show that it was equitable and also lowering the chance of anyone backing out during the battle.

After receiving the martial sword, Long Chen directly returned it to Shi Feng. Placing the crystal card into his robes, he couldn’t help but become somewhat excited.

Although five thousand gold coins wasn’t very much, it could help settle a bit of the desperate situation his family was in. It had been very long since they had received a stipend from the empire, and nowadays the Long family was quickly reaching the point where they couldn’t even afford decent food to eat.

Under the attentive gazes of countless people, the two of them unhurriedly left. The two maidens watched Long Chen leave and immediately afterward, they also disappeared.

The news that Long Chen had beaten Li Hao seemed to gain legs as it rapidly spread. In just a short time, the entire imperial capital learned of it. The news puzzled countless people; how could trash who couldn’t practice martial arts possibly have become this difficult to deal with?

But even with so many people personally seeing it as well as the news that Li Hao had to be carried back to his estate, quite a few people were still incapable of completely accepting it.

Long Chen had wanted to split his earnings with Shi Feng, but Shi Feng was completely unwilling. In the end, he quickly made an excuse that he had things to do before hastily leaving, not even asking Long Chen how he had suddenly become so powerful.

Remembering this favor in his heart, Long Chen directly went to the Hundred Herb Market. Entering into the Hundred Herb Market, Long Chen requested a catalog of their medicinal ingredients.

On it were very clear recordings of the various medicinal ingredients’ names and prices. Long Chen saw the majority of the medicinal ingredients required to refine the FengFu Pill[1]. It was quite lucky that the medicinal ingredients for the FengFu Pill were not especially uncommon.

However, looking at the price, Long Chen’s heart practically dripped blood. The gold coins he had now were only enough to buy three portions of the medicinal ingredients.

But he couldn’t spend it all on these medicinal ingredients since he still needed to buy a medicinal furnace for refining, as well as to buy some other spare medicinal ingredients. The few gold coins he had were like a cup of water trying to put out a burning cart.

However, not buying it was also unacceptable, so Long Chen clenched his teeth and spent twelve hundred gold coins to buy a bronze furnace of the worst quality.

He also bought one set of the medicinal ingredients for the FengFu Pill as well as a large amount of medicinal ingredients for the Energy Recovery Powder. By the time Long Chen left the Hundred Herb Market, the amount on his crystal card was only five hundred gold coins.

After returning home, Long Chen went right to his own room. Firmly locking the door, he ordered Bao-er to tell everyone that he was not to be disturbed.

He knew that his mother would hear the news that he had once again gone to compete in martial arts. Afraid that his mother would worry, he purposely told Bao-er to block her. In any case, nothing had happened to him, and his mother shouldn’t become too concerned.

Right now, he had to seize every second of every minute to quickly increase his strength. He was sure that the current Long family’s predicament was not as simple as it seemed, and he sensed the coming of a crisis.

The spiritual energy in Long Chen’s body started moving, and a cluster of flame appeared within his hand. This was a pill cultivator’s agglomerated Pill Flame. But when Long Chen saw this ball of flame, he didn’t know whether to laugh or cry; this flame was far too weak. The Pill Flame was formed from a pill cultivator’s spiritual energy, and through special operating methods it was condensed into a spiritual energy flame. However, the current Long Chen’s Pill Flame’s temperature was extremely low, even when compared to other ordinary Pill Flames.

In addition, Long Chen found that without his Dantian to support him, he couldn’t maintain the Pill Flame for more than a quarter of an hour, which was far from enough time to refine medicinal pills.

Long Chen bitterly smiled. However, luckily he had his backup plan, which was first refining the Energy Recovery Powder. Placing the medicinal ingredients into the furnace, he refined them one by one. This time, he didn’t use his Pill Flame, but instead used a normal fire from the wood.

When all the medicinal ingredients had been refined, he placed them into a jug of water to form Energy Recovery Liquid and after resting for a short period of time, Long Chen took a deep breath and prepared himself to officially begin the refining of FengFu Pill.

[1] FengFu is an acupuncture point on the back of the neck. Feng=wind, while Fu refers to the location of a place that controls something. The name means that that location is the point where the flow of breath within the body is controlled.

Chapter 4 Condensing the FengFu Star

Nine Yin Grass, refinement complete.

Earth Dragon Root, refinement complete.

Flame Seed, refinement complete.

….

Over thirty types of medicinal herbs were refined one by one, using up over two hours of Long Chen’s time and causing him to be covered in sweat.

Refining pills was not the same as simply decocting medicine. Every single medicinal herb’s essence had to be extracted while at the same time removing the impurities, forming a powder.

However, the flame in Long Chen’s hand was of far too low a quality and the refined powder still retained too many impurities to be ideal. Still, this was the only method that he had.

First of all, Long Chen’s cultivation base was nonexistent, and thus he didn’t have the necessary strength to sustain the Pill Flame, making its strength weak.

Second of all, currently, Long Chen didn’t have the opportunity or capability to subdue a different flame, so he could only settle for what he had.

But wanting to train in alchemy methods required not only a strong Pill Flame but also forceful spiritual energy, and the most important requirement was an exceedingly powerful Spiritual Strength.

The other two requirements were not that difficult. As for the Pill Flame, as long as you made all the proper preparations, you could seize a fire-attribute Magical Beast and gradually tame it into a house pet. Drawing on the Magical Beast’s flame, you could subdue it and cultivate it to become your own flame.

Over ninety-nine percent of capable alchemists used beast flames. Only a handful of people, who possessed extremely ancient inheritances of powerful strength, could control those extremely mysterious and mystical Spirit Flames found within heaven and earth.

Spirit Flames were flames that possessed their own soul and according to Long Chen’s memories, he had previously controlled an extremely formidable Spirit Flame.

But no matter how formidable he was in the past, right now he could only use this trash flame for his pill refining. After all, the things in his memories were not things he could take out.

After resting enough, Long Chen took a deep breath. He placed a candle into his hand and a yellow flame appeared.

“Not bad, after going through the refinements, the flame’s strength has increased by a slight amount. Whatever, it’s better than nothing I guess.”

After consecutively refining seven different medicines’ essence, he threw them into the furnace. His Spiritual Strength erupted out and the flame in Long Chen’s hand suddenly fluctuated. Compared to before, it was now several times stronger.

“Using Spiritual Strength to support the flame. If other alchemists saw this, wouldn’t they be shocked to death?” Long Chen bitterly smiled.

Spiritual Strength was the foundation of any pill refinement. At the time of refining, a large amount of Spiritual Strength was needed in order to control the temperature. If even a slight deviation occurred, it would waste all of your previous efforts and you would end up refining a pile of pill ashes. Moreover, if the medicinal pill had a very large medicinal strength, then you might even cause a furnace explosion.

Most alchemists wouldn’t start using their Spiritual Strength right at the beginning of the refinement. They would only use it towards the latter stages, when the pill was about to take form in order to very carefully control the flame’s strength.

After all, that was the critical time in the formation of the pill. At that time, the flame’s temperature had to constantly change, sometimes high and sometimes low, and doing so required a large consumption of Spiritual Strength.

If at that time, the alchemist’s Spiritual Strength was already exhausted, then the furnace of pills could basically be considered as scrapped. However, Long Chen actually started using his Spiritual Strength right at the beginning of the refinement.

In addition, he used this precious Spiritual Strength just in order to increase the flame’s power, treating it like firewood. Any alchemist would definitely rage and curse at him for doing so. Even if someone was a reckless and frivolous spender, no one would actually spend it like this.

But Long Chen wasn’t worried. According to his memories, his Spiritual Strength was already not lacking compared to ordinary alchemists.

Pill cultivator ranks were Pill Apprentice, Pill Adept, Pill Master, Pill King, Pill Emperor, Pill Ancestor, Pill Venerate, Pill Saint, and Pill Sovereign.

The FengFu Pill was a first tier medicinal pill and generally, pill cultivators who had reached the Pill Apprentice rank could refine a first tier medicinal pill.

Long Chen’s current memories also included those of a Pill Sovereign, so he was completely clear on his current capabilities. When Long Chen had awoken, his Spiritual Strength had changed to become abnormally strong compared to his previous trash self; therefore, Long Chen was qualified to use his Spiritual Strength in such a manner.

The pill furnace in front of Long Chen faintly trembled, emitting a slight buzzing noise.

“Hehe, by increasing the power of the flame, the speed has increased by quite a bit.”

He hastily threw in three more medicinal ingredients into the furnace; however, Long Chen’s forehead was already perspiring at this moment.

Hurriedly taking out a straw, he placed one end into the medicine jar which was filled with Energy Recovery Liquid and quickly drank a mouthful.

When the Energy Recovery Liquid entered his stomach, the pores all over his body opened and began to crazily absorb the spiritual energy between and heaven and earth. His originally about-to-be exhausted spiritual energy rapidly recovered.

This was what Long Chen had prepared earlier. Without it, there was no way for him to refine the FengFu Pill. With his current level, it would be a joke if he could actually refine a pill on his own without some kind of assistance.

With the straw in his mouth, every now and then he would draw in another mouthful of Energy Recovery Liquid to replenish his body’s spiritual energy.

With Long Chen’s spiritual energy being replenished, his Spiritual Strength could show off how extremely powerful it was, and it was only two days later that Long Chen started to feel a bit exhausted. That was a sign that his Spiritual Strength had been largely used up.

However, at this time, the medicinal ingredients had already been absorbed into the pill furnace, so all that was left was finishing up. The medicinal aroma was also starting to fill the air.

Although Long Chen’s impression of a first tier medicinal pill was that it was so easy to refine it could be done with his eyes closed, the current him was no longer the same Pill Sovereign in his memories. His destiny had already been completely changed and saying that he wasn’t nervous would be a lie.

Buzz.

Suddenly, the pill furnace’s interior started to vibrate, emitting a series of buzzing noises. The energy within the pill furnace also started to become berserk.

Long Chen didn’t become even the slightest bit panicked; on the contrary, he even started to smile. This was the indication of the pill’s formation and also the most critical time of the refinement.

His Spiritual Strength was completely activated with not even a trace of it held in reserve. The flame in his hand suddenly exploded out, and an incorporeal strength tightly sealed the entire pill furnace. This technique was called ‘Heaven Seal Earth Lock’ and was something that he had come up with from his memories. It was something used in order to prevent pill explosions and also, furnace explosions.

Moreover, this technique was very practical and could in the shortest period seal the medicinal energy within the pill furnace, not letting much leak out.

Normal alchemists would all do this at the last step because when the medicinal pill would go berserk, it was possible to stabilize it by taking a more gentle action.

Although doing so would decrease the danger by a lot, a large amount of the medicinal essence would be lost, and therefore, the medicinal pill’s quality would just be ordinary.

Bang!

Following the full suppression of Long Chen’s Spiritual Strength, the pill furnace emitted a smothered noise. After that, everything turned silent.

The pill furnace had already turned tranquil. Long Chen couldn’t help but to gasp for breath. His whole body was drenched in sweat, and he was so dizzy that he felt the sky was spinning.

When he felt a bit better, he excitedly opened up the furnace. His hand was even trembling as he picked out five extremely round pills. Holding them in his hand, a dense medicinal aroma completely filled the whole room.

“Two low-grade pills and three trash pills. Tch, saying it out loud really makes me lose enough face to die.” Long Chen’s face was showing how excited he was, but he still sighed.

Staring blankly for a bit, he couldn’t help but laugh. He had a mixture of a lifetime’s worth of memories from a Pill Sovereign along with the memories of his current self. Apparently, that Pill Sovereign was truly excessively arrogant.

He himself didn’t care about losing any face though, and he hastily carefully examined the pills in his hand.

There were two low-grade medicinal pills with their bodies completely round and their pill aroma filling the air. The aroma refreshed the mind and raised a person’s spirit when smelled.

Long Chen couldn’t hold back a burst of elation. After all, one successful medicinal pill could be sold in the imperial capital for at least ten thousand gold coins.

In addition, even the three trash pills in his hand were much better than the medicinal pill his mother had bought for him, especially since at least thirty percent of the medicinal essence had been sealed into the pill.

A medicinal pill that had locked in fifty percent of the essence would be termed low grade, and over eighty percent of all medicinal pills were only low grade.

If the medicinal essence reached sixty percent it would be middle grade, seventy percent would make it high grade, eighty percent would make it top grade, ninety percent would make it peerless grade, and as for one hundred percent… hehe. Right now Long Chen didn’t think too much about it as it was simply too far for his current self.

Some people might wonder about the difference between fifty and sixty percent content of medicinal essence. Was it a significant difference?

Wouldn’t consuming two low-grade medicinal pills be much more effective than one middle grade? If someone heard you ask this question, they’d probably choke on their own spit.

Inside a medicinal pill was not only its medicinal essence but also impurities. These impurities were unable to be absorbed by the body, and most importantly, these impurities would cancel out a portion of the absorbed essence.

The saying that each medicine had its own side effects was not just a colloquial saying but a hard truth. During the formation of a pill, it was difficult to avoid accumulating pill toxins. These kinds of toxins, if not taken very often, would not have a large effect.

But for cultivators, medicinal pills were often life-saving measures, and who would know just how many pills you would consume in one lifetime. When the body’s pill toxins reached a certain degree, they would become a life-threatening poison.

Pill toxins were one of the most difficult to eliminate poisons. They penetrated deep into the flesh and bones and even the spirit. But the higher grade a medicinal pill was, the fewer toxins it would have.

It was for this reason that the medicinal effect of a middle-grade medicinal pill was over ten times greater than a low-grade medicinal pill. As for the price difference, it was at least a hundred times greater.

After collecting the five medicinal pills and cleaning up the medicinal furnace, Long Chen could no longer endure it and collapsed into slumber.

After sleeping for an unknown amount of time, he felt two hands caressing his cheek and could hear some low-pitched murmurings, but he was too exhausted and incapable of waking up.

When Long Chen once again regained consciousness, it was already three days later. His stomach was growling with hunger, and he wolfed down his food before once again starting his seclusion.

Consuming one trash pill, he used his Spiritual Strength to guide the medicinal pill’s energy to enter the YongQuan point[1] on the bottom of his foot. That was the location of the first Star of the Nine Star Hegemon Body Art - the position of the FengFu Star.

BANG!

Long Chen’s left foot shook. The intense energy came from the bottom of his foot, and the ground under it became covered in cracks.

“Excellent, I’ve already found the meridian channel as well as the exact position. Now I can genuinely attack it.”

Long Chen faintly smiled, and he took out a low tier FengFu Pill and directly consumed it. The pure and perfect energy erupted and under Long Chen’s pull, it went straight to the YongQuan point on the bottom of his foot.

The YongQuan point trembled. Following the rushing medicinal energy, it was just like a dry riverbed receiving water, and it crazily convulsed.

BOOM!

A booming noise reverberated, and the frightening energy filled Long Chen’s whole body. The tyrannical energy exploded out of its own accord, shaking the room into smoke and dust, with waves of energy surging about.

As the smoke and dust slowly scattered, it exposed a tranquil and refined Long Chen; his eyes filled with excitement. He could sense a pea-sized body on the bottom of his foot from which endless energy would flow out into his body, giving Long Chen a desire to lift his head up to the heavens and roar.

The activity from Long Chen’s room caused the entire noble estate to be disturbed, and everyone rushed over.

Seeing his mother also coming over, Long Chen hastily said, “Mom, today is the day that the noble heirs can enter the Imperial College to study, I have to hurry over.”

After saying this, he left behind a group of dumbstruck people and a pile of destroyed ruins, as he changed into clean clothes and left directly for the Imperial College.

[1] The YongQuang point涌泉穴, literally meaning gushing/bubbling springs acupuncture point, is found on the bottom of the foot 2/3 of the way up in the middle. In the five-element system, the kidney meridian is water element, and since the foot is always touching the ground, the YongQuan point is earth element. The kidney meridian connects to the YongQuan point, thus it is ‘gushing springs point’, the point where the water element flows into the earth element. In Qigong, it connects us to the ground, and through the point at the top of the head, it allows us to pull in the energy of heaven and earth through us. In acupuncture it is used to treat orders in the head and neck and is also used to calm the spirit.

Chapter 5 Imperial College

The Imperial College opened its doors one day every month for the imperial capital’s noble heirs. In the morning, they would practice poetry and etiquette, and in the afternoon, the palace’s martial arts depository would be available to everyone free of charge.

The previous openings of the Imperial College held absolutely no meaning to Long Chen since even if he attended, he would just be the object of ridicule for everyone there.

But now that was no longer the case. After consuming the FengFu Pill, Long Chen had already condensed an embryonic form of the FengFu Star.

Although it was just an embryonic form and couldn’t store that much spiritual energy, it was still able to store much more than what could be stored in just the body’s meridians. After all, the meridians were like rivers while the Dantian was like the ocean that fed the rivers, even sometimes being called the ‘energy sea’.

Although a river might appear large, its capacity was limited. Without the Dantian to support it, it would quickly be used up. But this problem was completely resolved with the condensing of the FengFu Star. And the most important thing was that now that the embryonic form of the FengFu Star had been condensed, as long as there was enough energy, it would eventually become a complete FengFu Star.

At that time, Long Chen would have something unique to himself to use as a ‘Dantian’. This was the most unique point of the Nine Star Hegemon Body Art.

When all nine stars were condensed, it would be equivalent to having nine Dantians. Anyone could understand just how powerful that kind of forceful spiritual energy source was.

Long Chen was in possession of the entire Nine Star Hegemon Body Art. Unfortunately, such a cultivation technique was something that defied the heavens, and his understanding of it was still very low, so he still needed to spend an endless amount of meditation on it.

Once he managed to completely condense his FengFu Star, he would be able to store an extremely large amount of spiritual energy. Then he could attempt to agglomerate his blood vessels and enter the Blood Condensation stage, thus becoming a true martial artist.

The Qi Condensation stage was just the first step of training in martial arts. Only by stepping into the Blood Condensation stage, having your blood and qi surge, and having your martial powers sharply rise, only then could you be considered a genuine martial artist.

Long Chen didn’t know what Heavenstage of Qi Condensation he would count as, but with the formation of his embryonic FengFu Star, his body’s strength had been increased by a surprising amount.

The current him could let out a very simple punch, and it would cause the wind to whistle, so much so that the force it generated would have enough power to break apart a vase even two meters away. Essentially, it was like his whole body was brimming with strength.

His goal in going to the Imperial College this time was to enter the martial arts depository. With his FengFu Star’s embryonic form, his body’s spiritual energy had risen, and he could already begin to train in martial Battle Skills.

These so-called Battle Skills were all created by extremely powerful seniors. They were powerful fighting techniques that used a person’s spiritual energy, qi, and meridians.

Battle Skills were extremely terrifying. They could allow a martial artist to release an extremely formidable power that was several times stronger than their ordinary strength. It was impossible to be courageous in front of them.

Therefore, each Battle Skill was extremely important to a martial artist. Now that Long Chen had spiritual energy capable of training in Battle Skills, he was itching to obtain one.

The Imperial College was located to the north side of the imperial capital. It spanned tens of kilometers, and other than the Imperial Palace, it was the grandest and most imposing building in the entire imperial capital.

After Long Chen showed off his identification plate, he entered into the Imperial College and went straight to the literature hall. That was where the morning lecture took place and where the noble heirs would listen to the studies of the Dao from lecturers talking about everything and anything, from etiquette to poetry, and even to ancient theories of literature.

Entering into the literature hall, he saw that due to how early he was, the extremely large literature hall only had several dozen people.

“Haha, brother Long, you came.”

Just as Long Chen entered, several youths came over and cordially greeted him.

These youths were similar to Long Chen; for various reasons, they also had no way of cultivating. Although they couldn’t be considered best friends, they were still fellow sufferers who empathized with each other.

In the golden age of martial arts in the Phoenix Cry Empire, these youths might not have been bullied in such a miserable way as Long Chen, but they were also frequently sneered at and suffered from a cold and indifferent treatment.

Thus, these people who suffered from similar torments ended up becoming closer to Long Chen. They were especially glad to see him now since it had been a long time since they’d seen each other.

“Haha, you guys came here pretty early,” Long Chen laughingly greeted. With the success of the condensation of his FengFu Star, his mood had improved greatly from the formerly depressed him.

“I heard a few days ago that brother Long put up a huge display of his awesome power, defeating Li Hao. Ah, you really make us admire you. Don’t tell me that brother Long can actually genuinely cultivate now?” one skinny teen extremely enviously asked.

Originally, they were all the same level as Long Chen. Hearing that Long Chen could actually defeat Li Hao who was at the third Heavenstage of Qi Condensation, they were all extremely shocked while also feeling a slight jealousy.

“Hehe, it was just luck. But most recently, I did learn a new Divine Technique.” Long Chen didn’t want to continue on this subject, so he brought up a new mysterious topic.

“Divine Technique? What’s that?” Sure enough, everyone immediately became distracted by this new change in subject.

“Hehe, this little brother recently obtained a rare clairvoyance book, and after painstakingly reading this book, I learned quite a few things,” Long Chen said somewhat complacently.

“Clairvoyance technique? Isn’t that just what the fortune tellers on the streets use to scam people?”

“Not quite. With what I learned from that clairvoyance technique, I saw that Li Hao’s face had a dark omen of misfortune on it, and it was only then that I decided to duel with him. And as for the result… hehe.” Long Chen laughed and stopped there.

Everyone was dubious for a moment when someone suddenly brightened with understanding and exclaimed, “It seems to be true! I heard that Li Hao seemed to have been bewitched that day, and his whole body didn’t have even the slightest bit of energy before he was defeated by brother Long. “

The details of Long Chen and Li Hao’s battle were known to everyone, but there were many people who felt that Li Hao’s defeat was quite a deep mystery. Nowadays, there was a great deal of discussion over Long Chen.

“Hehe, brother Long, since you are proficient in reading faces, can you help take a look at me and tell me why my fiancée always avoids me? Why won’t she agree to see me?” one person somewhat vexingly asked.

“No problem. Come, come, let’s first find a place for us all to sit. Standing here is somewhat unsuitable.”

Their group found a table in the corner to sit at, and the table even had some refreshments for them.

Long Chen pointed towards the table’s desserts and laughingly told everyone, “Let’s all eat a piece.”

“Ok,” the other people didn’t stand on courtesy and all took a piece. Everyone seemed a bit confused as they looked at Long Chen.

“How’s the taste?”

“Very good.”

“Let’s eat another piece?”

“Ok.”

That person once again picked up a piece and took a bite. But when he had only eaten one bite, his face suddenly brightened, and he respectfully turned towards Long Chen and said, “Many thanks for brother Long’s advice. This little brother understands now. I was being too greedy and brother Long was reminding me that people need to be content with their situation, right?”

Everyone looked at Long Chen in admiration. Who would have thought that Long Chen had the profound skills to use some small desserts as food for thought? However, Long Chen still sighed and shook his head. “Wrong. What I wanted to remind you of is that you’re already this fat, and yet you’re still eating this much. Soon you won’t even be able to fit through the door. The fact that your fiancée is still with you and hasn’t left you is already an enormous accommodation; you should be happy with just that. With a body shape like yours, any woman would be scared to sleep beside you. What if you rolled over in your sleep? You’d crush her so hard, she’d turn flat.”

That person’s face reddened, and with Long Chen’s reminder, he looked at his five foot tall height with his four and a half foot wide stomach. Apparently, he had previously felt that he had only fattened by a little bit.

“Fatty Yu, don’t waste brother Long’s precious time; hurry up and go lose some weight. Big bro Long, hehe, how about you take a shot at reading my face?” A different slender youth respectfully asked with a smile.

“Oh, you?” Long Chen made a big show of acting very seriously as he looked at him for quite a while before saying, “Your face ordains that before you are thirty, you will be destitute and frustrated, but the good thing is that after you are thirty…”

That person became jubilant, saying, “Is it possible that after thirty I can suddenly rise in my cultivation?”

“No. After you are thirty you will slowly become accustomed to your situation and will no longer be frustrated,” said Long Chen.

“…”

Everyone couldn’t help but to burst into laughter, but just as they were laughing, they suddenly saw two bitter eyes staring at them, causing everyone’s laughter to break off.

Long Chen had long since noticed that person. Turning around, they all saw Li Hao glaring daggers at them.

“Senior Li Hao, are your wounds better now? Congratulations! Your outer wounds are all healed, but what about your inner wounds?” Long Chen asked, seeming deeply concerned.

Li Hao’s face twitched. That day, his face had been smashed flat by Long Chen, and he had needed to be carried home. The Li family had hurriedly asked for the help of an alchemist from the alchemist guild and paid an extremely large sum of gold coins to help Li Hao recover.

Having money was truly good; in such a short time, Li Hao had already returned to a point where he looked the same as a normal person.

But after Long Chen brought the subject back up, Li Hao’s groin started to hurt as if he was remembering that one kick from Long Chen.

At that time, Long Chen’s kick had been very vicious, just a little bit off from turning him into a cripple. The thing that pissed him off the most though was that only after he got carried home and healed did he notice that he was missing a certain something. When his estate noticed this, they hurriedly rushed back to the martial arena, but by that time, they found that the arena had already been cleaned, and it was reported that something had been taken away by a wild dog.

When Li Hao had woken up and heard this news, he almost died from his anger. But now there was no way to fix it, and no matter how amazing an alchemist was, there was no way for them to fix what he had lost.

What had been two was now only one. Although the loss of one family jewel wouldn’t tilt him while walking, the loss of the originally symmetric pair was hard on him.

And now that Long Chen had brought it back up, his face became exceedingly ugly. He glared daggers at Long Chen, his teeth grinding in fury. “Long Chen, you son of a bitch. I challenge you to a life and death duel! Do you dare to accept?”

Long Chen’s originally amused expression tensed immediately. Being called in such a way was exceedingly insulting, especially since it also insulted his mother.

It really was the case of not knowing to value one’s life. Fine, if you want to be free from the mortal world’s worries, then I’ll help you.

“Same thing as before. I want to add stakes.”

Long Chen stared back at Li Hao. Since you want to die, you had best offer me up some benefits. Although they came from the same empire, he didn’t care about Li Hao, and his death would be trifling to him.

“Fine! No matter how high you make the stakes, I, Li Hao, will accept.” Sneering in his mind, he thought to himself that no matter how high the stakes were, once Long Chen was dead, there was no way he could spend it. Li Hao was under the impression that last time he had simply been careless, and Long Chen had grabbed onto that opening and thus he had lost. Now he would definitely not make the same mistake, so this fight would definitely not go the same way as the last fight.

In addition, this time was different in that he had declared a life-or-death duel; in last time’s duel, although you would not be held responsible for killing your opponent with a blow, as long as the opponent conceded, it was not permitted to continue attacking them.

But in a life-or-death duel, once the two people went onto the stage, it was equivalent to putting their lives on the line. Even if someone admitted defeat, it would be useless. The victor could do as he pleased. The loser’s life would be in their hands.

“Ok, tomorrow, three quarters after noon, we will meet on the life and death stage.” Li Hao coldly laughed, and when he looked at Long Chen, it was like he was staring at a dead person.

Long Chen coldly sneered inside. Now was the time for him to kill a chicken to warn the monkeys. Seeing Li Hao leave, he slyly laughed, “Careful to stay balanced while walking; don’t trip.”

Hearing Long Chen’s words, Li Hao, who had already turned to leave, stiffened, and his face became contorted as he inferred the hidden meaning behind Long Chen’s words.

Taking a deep breath, he acted like he hadn’t heard anything as he slowly walked to a different part of the literature hall.

But Long Chen’s words seemed to be like a steel needle piercing through his sensitive parts, and every time he lifted his leg, it would trigger memories of that bone-chilling attack.

He continued to act as if nothing had happened, but the more he tried to do so, the more unnatural his gait became, which caused everyone to stare strangely over at him. In the end, Li Hao waddled away similar to a duck.

One person turned to Long Chen and reminded him to be careful, “Brother Long, why did you accept his challenge? This is a life and death battle you’re going into; one of you will end up dying!”

“No problem. Today I read his face and saw a dark aura of death around him. With it twisting around him, it’s basically like a ghost sealing his life; he’s doomed to die within two days. That’s right, I now have something that I need a few people’s help with,” whispered Long Chen.

Everyone exchanged glances and in the end, the person who had been nicknamed fatty Yu clenched his teeth. “Brother Long, since you’ve asked, I’ll give you my entire savings.”

Saying this, he handed over a crystal card to Long Chen. Long Chen hadn’t expected that this fatty Yu would actually have such a strong spirit of brotherhood with him. His crystal card had over eighty thousand gold coins on it.

Although they were all noble heirs, mostly they were born in far off branches, so they weren’t considered very important. These gold coins should be an extremely large sum to fatty Yu.

“Fine, I have sixty thousand here, take it.”

“I don’t have that much here, only thirty thousand. Brother Long, I only have this little capability.”

“I have…”

Originally, Long Chen had thought that just borrowing ten or so thousand gold coins would already be quite a lot. He hadn’t thought that they would actually completely empty their pockets to help him.

“Everyone, if by chance I were to die, then your money would basically be lost.” Long Chen looked at the crystal cards in his hand, and he couldn’t help but to give everyone a reminder.

“Does brother Long look down on us? None of us are capable of cultivating, and every day we have to suffer through other people’s torments. Brother Long, the fact that you dare go all-out in a battle against one of them means you have courage that none of us possess. Even if we don’t have your courage, helping you out this little bit is still something we can do.”

When these people saw Long Chen agree to the life and death battle, they couldn’t help but become excited since they were fighting a common enemy. Seeing Long Chen begging for help, they became even more heated and in the end, they didn’t even care about the consequences.

Long Chen nodded. He recorded this feeling in his heart as he held the over two hundred thousand gold coins in his hand.

At this moment, a group of people walked into the literature hall, and the originally noisy literature hall immediately turned completely silent.

Chapter 6 Collecting Interest

Long Chen turned to look at the people entering and his eyes turned cold. This group of people was hovering around one certain fellow, similar to how the stars flocked around the moon, groveling.

He seemed to be carved out of jade and appeared extremely handsome. He was none other than the person who had beaten Long Chen on the martial arena to the point where he had almost died, the Savage Marquis’s son, Zhou Yaoyang.

Zhou Yaoyang was the noble heir of the Savage Marquis, and his cultivation base was at the peak amongst his peers. Therefore, his popularity was very high amongst his fellow noble heirs.

Zhou Yaoyang immediately noticed Long Chen’s group, and smiling slightly, he walked over. Looking at Long Chen, he said, “Many apologies for what happened last time. I didn’t expect that my one blow would cause you to not even be able to recognize your own mother.”

Although he spoke words of regret, his face didn’t have even the slightest trace of apology. His words were filled with disdain, just like he was a king far above looking down on Long Chen.

“Don’t worry about it. Very soon I’ll beat you to the point where you don’t even recognize your own grandmother.” Long Chen indifferently smiled, but inside he was secretly furious.

When he had awoken that day, only his mother and that old alchemist had been there. Therefore, this news must have been transmitted by that old stick.

Zhou Yaoyang’s one sentence was equivalent to him telling Long Chen that the old alchemist had been one of his people. And furthermore, Long Chen’s injury that day might have been extremely frightening, but in reality, it wasn’t actually a life-threatening injury. Even the injury on the back of his head had only appeared bad due to the amount of blood, but it was not actually too severe.

Therefore, there had basically been no point in using an expensive medicinal pill in order to treat it. The old alchemist had clearly been trying to frighten his mother and make sure that he could suck up all of their savings.

Something like that basically had no benefit for himself, but instead weakened the Long family’s resources. With their current living situation, it was like adding hail onto snow. To think that there was actually such a hidden plot behind his back…

“Long Chen, are you looking to die? I think that you seem to have forgotten the pain now that your wounds have healed. Don’t tell me you want to once again be beaten half dead by brother Yaoyang?”

“That’s right, the trash who’s incapable of cultivating actually dares to open his mouth viciously. He’s obviously looking to die.”

“What an idiot. Letting such an idiot count as a noble heir is just an insult to us.”

Zhou Yaoyang didn’t even need to speak before the people beside him began cursing Long Chen, their saliva spraying wildly.

“Long Chen, you might be a noble heir like me, but one of us is in the heavens while one of us is on the ground. You are just a small ant, and all you can do is stare up at me. Therefore, even if I am bullying you, all you can do is suffer in silence. Otherwise, the consequences will be just like last time, and you will end up being beaten into a dead dog,” said Zhou Yaoyang, lifting a finger to point at Long Chen’s nose.

POW!

Long Chen indifferently smiled, and suddenly, he extended his hand; before anyone could react, he tightly clenched onto Zhou Yaoyang’s extended finger. Using a slight amount of force, a snapping noise rang out.

Zhou Yaoyang emitted a miserable cry as the pain of his snapped finger shook his whole body. His Ten Finger One Heart technique was actually so easily broken and snapped by Long Chen!

Even though he was a strong person at the seventh Heavenstage of Qi Condensation, as long as a person hadn’t stepped into the Blood Condensation realm, they would still only be slightly stronger than ordinary people.

In addition, he had been taken by surprise, so he hadn’t had time to defend himself, meaning he was basically no different than an ordinary person.

Long Chen condescendingly looked down on Zhou Yaoyang whose face was contorted in pain, and with a questioning tone, he asked, “You think you’re above others? Others are nothing to you? Are you sure you’re not talking about yourself?”

The sudden unexpected turn of events shocked everyone, and Zhou Yaoyang was in such pain that he was unable to reply. Only then did the others react and throw themselves at Long Chen.

“Bastard, hurry up and release brother Yaoyang!” When the others following Zhou Yaoyang saw that Long Chen had dared to attack him, they all shouted and swarmed around him.

“Whoever dares come over will be beaten by me.” Just as they were about to reach him, a large figure suddenly appeared beside Long Chen and furiously bellowed at the others with a thunderous roar, shaking their eardrums.

Long Chen smiled when he saw who it was. Who else could it be but Shi Feng?

The noble heirs, who were about to charge forward, stopped when they saw it was Shi Feng.

Shi Feng was someone who was proud and aloof, and he didn’t like being pulled into any certain social group. However, his cultivation base was top tier amongst the noble heirs, and adding on his large and superior stature, he managed to intimidate everyone into stepping back.

For a moment, everyone descended into silence, and the only sound in the whole literature hall was the pained moans from Zhou Yaoyang.

“What are you guys doing?!” Suddenly, an angry rebuke came over from the side, and an old man walked over. Everyone’s expression became much more timid and respectful when they saw this old man.

This old man was one of the lecturers of the literature hall. He was a Confucian scholar, and it was known that he was an honest and strict person, a dignified man who spoke few words.

“Fighting within the literature hall is punishable by one month’s custody. Do you guys want to try it out?” the old man coldly snorted.

Long Chen released Zhou Yaoyang’s finger which was already crushed and bent. Hurriedly turning towards the old man, he smiled, “Teacher, you’ve misunderstood. We weren’t fighting; we were just doing a test.”

“Oh? A test hmm? What kind of test?” The old man obviously wasn’t so easily hoodwinked, and he coldly questioned Long Chen.

“We were testing how long the strength of one finger could hold out against the attack of five fingers. Through this test, we reached the conclusion that the power of cooperation is something that cannot be stopped. No matter how strong a finger is, it is still isolated. Its power will weaken from time to time, and only by relying on a partner can power be released in a steady flow, making it stronger and more enduring. This time’s test allowed both Zhou Yaoyang and I to obtain an understanding of how to properly use the power of cooperation, and it will have an extremely large benefit towards our future cultivation. Brother Zhou, what do you think about these benefits, hmm?” Long Chen summarized, as he stared with a hidden meaning at Zhou Yaoyang.

Zhou Yaoyang was angered to the point of nearly passing out, but this grievance could only be swallowed by him, or if he denied it, he would be sent into custody with Long Chen. Even a noble heir couldn’t break the literature hall’s rules.

“Yes, that’s right.” Zhou Yaoyang did his best to keep his voice calm, but the pain was causing even his voice to sound rough.

The old man looked at Long Chen, and a trace of ridicule flashed within his eyes. But in the end, he still nodded and said, “Since it was like this, this old man won’t blame the two of you. But remember, in the future, you cannot make a ruckus in here.”

Everyone secretly sighed that Long Chen had good luck when they heard this. The old man clearly knew that Long Chen was just making up nonsense, but he still let them all go.

“Hey, wait.” Zhou Yaoyang clenched his teeth, and by using a voice that only the two of them could hear, he called out to Long Chen.

Long Chen’s hand attack had been extremely vicious; not only had it broken his finger, but in addition, he had used some kind of unknown method in order to turn the meridians within his finger into mush. Otherwise, Zhou Yaoyang would not be in such intense pain and end up as such a sorry figure without the slightest strength to fight back.

“Brother Zhou, feel free to come find me again to do some tests.”

Today is just a small payment on the interest I owe to you bastard. The worst is yet to come... But on the outside, Long Chen just courteously smiled.

Over two hundred noble heirs calmly and quietly took their seats. The old man nodded his head in satisfaction and started the lecture. However, his material was vague and incomprehensible to them, and basically, all of it fell on deaf ears. It caused everyone to become drowsy, but no one actually dared to sleep.

Although that old man didn’t have the slightest cultivation base, within the entire Imperial College, he had the final say in everything. If anyone angered him, they would immediately be kicked out and could just forget about entering the martial arts depository in the afternoon.

“This can be compared to chicken eggs; one has gone bad and one is still good. But if you want to eat the good egg, you have to eat the bad egg first...”

The old man continued to talk about all sorts of things… history, classical works, how to rule a flourishing nation, agricultural knowledge… even Long Chen almost dozed off.

However, people like fatty Yu actually listened very attentively. They couldn’t cultivate, so they had to rely on education for their future, hopefully obtaining some work with the government.

Under this slow torment, the time slowly passed until it was noon. After eating lunch, everyone swarmed towards the Battle Skill Pavilion.

Even the people who had no way of cultivating also followed. Within the Battle Skill Pavilion were countless Battle Skills and cultivation techniques, and going through them might offer them a lucky encounter.

The Battle Skill Pavilion had three floors, but only the bottom level was opened to all the noble heirs.

Even though it was just one floor, there were still seventeen bookshelves completely packed with all kinds of Battle Skills and cultivation techniques. It was a brilliant sight that dazzled people.

“Big brother Yaoyang, I already have a life-and-death battle agreement with Long Chen. This time I’ll definitely kill him to help take revenge for you,” Li Hao respectfully said. Who knew when, but Li Hao had at some point stealthily ran over beside Zhou Yaoyang.

At this point, Zhou Yaoyang had already used his energy in order to suppress the pain in his finger, but the important thing was that the meridians had been fried, and so he had to find an alchemist to help him treat it.

“It’s still not the right time to kill him; otherwise, I would have killed him last time.” Zhou Yaoyang shook his head. Suddenly he asked, “That’s right, how did you end up getting beaten up by him last time?”

“Ai, actually, it was just me being careless, and Long Chen happened to catch that opportunity. The result really infuriated me; to think that the trash could actually beat me once.” Li Hao answered with endless regret.

That one loss had caused his reputation to plummet, and the people whispering and gossiping about him behind his back drove him crazy with anger. He believed that last time was simply a small moment of carelessness, and so this time, he definitely had quite a bit of killing intent towards Long Chen.

“Long Chen cannot be permitted to die, at least not for now. Don’t mess this up.” Zhou Yaoyang worried that Li Hao hadn’t understood, so he purposely repeated himself.

“Then what should I do? Just let him off like this?” Li Hao somewhat unwillingly asked.

Zhou Yaoyang looked at his twisted broken finger, and while grinding his teeth in anger he said, “Although you can’t kill him, if you wanted to take back a couple of things on his body, that would be fine.”

When Li Hao heard this, his eyes brightened with excitement, “Excellent! This time, I’ll take what he took from me, and oh, I think I’ll also take one of his eyes too. Tch, seeing the expression in his eyes really pisses me off.”

Zhou Yaoyang and Li Hao grinned, but they didn’t notice that Long Chen, who was faking interest in the tomes, also smiled. However, his smile was much colder compared to theirs, like a leopard staring at two bleating sheep.

From Long Chen’s current position, he was perfectly placed so that he could use his Spiritual Strength to spy on what the two of them were talking about. Although he couldn’t hear what they were saying clearly, looking at their expressions, he could still infer most of it.

Observing the two of them start acting like nothing had happened and begin browsing the ancient tomes on the bookshelf, Long Chen was also disinclined to go deal with them. Instead, he switched to looking for his actual objective.

By now he had realized that the Pill Sovereign memories he had were actually extremely incomplete. Other than the Nine Star Hegemon Body Art, the rest of it only pertained to alchemy. There were no Battle Skills, so he absolutely needed to obtain one today.

Long Chen had finally settled on a Battle Skill and was just about to reach out his hand to take it when suddenly, a dark-faced fellow grabbed onto it before him.

“I’m sorry, this book has taken my fancy.”

That person didn’t even look at Long Chen, and acting like no one was beside him, he started browsing the tome.

Long Chen frowned slightly. This was done very obviously on purpose, but Long Chen didn’t take action, instead switching to a different bookcase.

Just as he saw a palm Battle Skill and reached out to take it, the dark-faced fellow who had long since been waiting to the side once again grabbed it.

“I’m sorry, this-”

POW!

A ruthless slap landed on that dark face, interrupting his words and sending him flying.

Chapter 7 Training in Battle Skills

POW!

An extremely loud and resounding slap rang out, ruthlessly interrupting that dark-faced fellow’s words. The powerful force sent him flying, and over ten teeth tumbled across the floor.

“I’m sorry, this tome has taken the fancy of this young master.”

Long Chen looked down at the dark-faced fellow with a face seemingly full of regret, apologizing with great flair.

That slap was very resounding, and it echoed throughout the entire Battle Skill Pavilion. Everyone who had been busily browsing the Battle Skills immediately put down the manuals in their hands and turned in shock.

“Who dares to be so presumptuous as to act violently within the Battle Skill Pavilion?!”

Suddenly, a cold shout rang out, and a black-clothed man appeared from the inner part of the Battle Skill Pavilion. His face was cold and strict as he looked at Long Chen and the dark-faced fellow.

That man’s blood and qi surged just like a towering mountain, pressuring the others and making it difficult for them to breathe. Long Chen’s pupils contracted…

“A strong Blood Condensation cultivator...”

It was unexpected that this place would actually have a hidden Blood Condensation realm cultivator. But thinking about it some more, this place was an important part of the Battle Skill Pavilion, and having a strong person keep guard would save them some worries.

It was forbidden to practice martial arts within the Battle Skill Pavilion. This was a rule that everybody knew, and breaking this rule meant you would be taken into custody.

“Speak, what happened here?” The Blood Condensation cultivator angrily shouted.

“If you want to know, then ask him.” Long Chen didn’t have the slightest amount of fear as he spread out his hands in innocence.

The dark-faced fellow became indignant. It was obviously him who had suffered the blow, so why would he still need to ask him? “Senior-”

“Senior!”

At this moment, the distant Zhou Yaoyang hurriedly ran over. He reported to the Blood Condensation expert, “Senior, it was like this: Wang Mang’s face suddenly felt extremely itchy, so he gave himself a slap. There really wasn’t any force or battle; you can check for yourself.”

The dark-faced fellow who was called Wang Mang became bewildered. But just as he was about to say something, he saw the distant Li Hao doing his best to give him a meaningful glance, so he swallowed his words back down.

“You’re the Savage Marquis’s son?”

“Yes.” Zhou Yaoyang hurriedly nodded.

That person nodded his head and looking at Wang Mang on the floor, he said, “If your face is itchy then just scratch it; don’t make such a fuss. Clean up after yourself. I don’t want to see such a situation a second time.”

After speaking, he turned and left, leaving a crowd of astonished people wondering why Zhou Yaoyang would actually help Long Chen.

“Haha, didn’t you hear what he said? Hurry up and clean up your crap.” Long Chen laughed as if he had totally expected this entire turn of events. Turning around, he walked away to continue looking for a Battle Skill.

“Hateful bastard.”

Looking at Long Chen who downplayed this event, Wang Mang was angered to the point where his eyes were practically spitting flames. That one slap of his caused him to feel extremely vexed.

“Wang Mang, endure it. If you were to open your mouth and accuse Long Chen of hitting you, then he would be taken into custody for one month, but after one month, he would be released safe and sound. However, if you swallow this anger now, then tomorrow, Li Hao will help you take back this face. Therefore, you must absolutely endure it.” Zhou Yaoyang informed him.

Wang Mang nodded his head. He knew that Li Hao had arranged a battle with Long Chen. But having bullied Long Chen for so long, he was already so accustomed to it that it had reached the point where it was just playing around.

However, today, his playing around had caused him to receive a huge slap in the face, and he didn’t even have a place to complain. The anger from the broken pieces of teeth could only be swallowed into his stomach.

A couple of people were busily picking up the scattered teeth and wiping off the bloodstains when Zhou Yaoyang suddenly asked, “The swelling on your face is very minor, so it appears that Long Chen’s strength is still not very high. But how is it that he managed to knock out so many of your teeth?”

The others were also very suspicious. According to common sense, only an extremely powerful force could knock out such sturdy teeth.

“Who knows? It’s completely ridiculous,” Wang Mang gloomily said. What he didn’t know was that Long Chen had used his knowledge as an alchemist. Long Chen was already as familiar with the human body’s physiology as he was with the back of his hands.

His slap had been struck in a skillful way so that Wang Mang’s gums would loosen, and the teeth on that side of his face had taken the opportunity to tumble out.

Long Chen’s attack had been very vicious. Teeth were not something that could be easily regrown; they were not like other injuries that could be healed with medicines. In the future, Wang Mang could probably only use the other side of his face to eat.

Having learned from Wang Mang’s mistake, everyone became much more well behaved and no one dared to once again provoke Long Chen.

Long Chen was also happy to leisurely browse through these ancient tomes. The Battle Skills here could only be read in the pavilion and could not be taken outside.

Spirit of the Bull.

All Battle Skills could be divided into three categories: Heaven, Earth, and Mortal. And as for all these Battle Skills and techniques here, all of them were merely the lowest level of the Mortal category.

Although they were the lowest level, these Battle Skills were still extremely precious treasures. Even though they were only for the high status noble heirs, it still required a Blood Condensation cultivator to oversee it. From this, one could see just how important Battle Skills were to the Phoenix Cry Empire.

“Although it’s a low grade Battle Skill, its usage of spiritual energy is clear and direct, making its effect pretty good.”

After completely reading through the Battle Skill in his hand, Long Chen nodded. This particular Battle Skill was very suited to him especially since he was extremely familiar with the body’s meridians, meaning he could master it very quickly.

He carefully read through it once again. His current Spiritual Strength was extremely formidable compared to a normal person, and it was a great assistance towards his memory. Essentially, he was almost at the point where he could remember anything he saw.

The Spirit of the Bull technique was completely memorized by him. Placing it back, he saw a different support Battle Skill, Windchasing Steps.

Windchasing Steps was a kind of footwork technique. Spiritual energy would flow through a set of specific meridians focusing around the feet, increasing one’s speed and explosiveness. Whether it was traversing large distances or short evasions, this technique was extremely effective.

“Excellent, another practical technique I can use.”

Long Chen faintly smiled, and once again busied himself to carefully remember all the routes of the spiritual energy and the details of how to do so.

“Time’s up, all noble heirs must put the tomes back. If anyone dares to secretly steal some, even death is not a harsh enough punishment!”

At this moment, the Blood Condensation cultivator once again appeared. His cold shout was transmitted to everyone’s ears, and everyone hurriedly placed back the tomes in their hands.

Several people, who still wanted to continue, sighed and shook their heads. The Phoenix Cry Empire was truly exceedingly strict with Battle Skills. Every month they would only have half a day to study here.

Many people had to spend several months’ time just to learn a single Battle Skill. But although they were discontented, no one would dare to complain.

Long Chen looked up slightly surprised. He hadn’t expected that the time would pass by this quickly. But if other people were to learn that Long Chen had used just a short four hours to completely memorize two Battle Skills, they might be shocked to the point that their jaws would hit the ground.

Within the recordings of a Battle Skill, there were the extremely cryptic and difficult to understand portions, especially with regards to some of the terms about moving spiritual energy and qi around specific meridians. And what confounded people even more was attempting to practice moving their spiritual energy in such a complicated way while also reading.

Leaving the Imperial College, Long Chen said his farewells to fatty Yu and the others before going up to Shi Feng and whispering a couple things.

When Shi Feng heard what Long Chen was saying, his whole face burst into shock, and although he quickly suppressed it back to his normal expression, he was unable to conceal the shock in his eyes.

Returning home, Long Chen saw that the room where he had condensed the FengFu Star had been cleaned up. However, it still wasn’t safe for people to live in yet due to how heavily he had damaged it. Luckily, his family estate had many rooms, and they had prepared a new one for him.

First, he went to his mother’s room in order to assure her that he was alright. Many things had consecutively come up during these days, causing Mrs. Long to become agitated and worried.

Ever since Long Chen woke up, it seemed like he had changed and become a completely different person, causing her to feel a bit of unfamiliarity.

However, the good thing was that Long Chen had already adjusted himself now, and after accompanying and talking to his mother for a while, she calmed down by quite a bit. Nonetheless, he didn’t tell her about the life and death battle that he had arranged with Li Hao.

Leaving his mother’s side, Long Chen returned to his room. Locking his door, he directly swallowed the second FengFu Pill.

Following the absorption of the second FengFu Pill, the FengFu Star on the bottom of Long Chen’s foot once again expanded ever so slightly.

Along with the expansion, the FengFu Star’s ability to store spiritual energy once again increased, just like a Dantian.

However, the current FengFu Star was still in an embryonic form, and in order for it to reach a fully condensed form, a countless number of FengFu Pills were still required.

That was also why Long Chen had been so dismayed when he had first gone through his memories and seen the method to train in the Nine Star Hegemon Body Art.

Currently, he had consumed two FengFu Pills that were worth several hundred thousand gold coins, and yet, his FengFu Star was still in its embryonic form. He was still extremely far off if he wanted it to reach the completely condensed stage. Furthermore, it seemed there was a level beyond even that, which was something he still didn’t know anything about. Just the one FengFu Star was already a bottomless abyss that needed countless medicinal pills to fill.

However, Long Chen knew that the Nine Star Hegemon Body Art was the only technique he could use. Otherwise, he would be just mediocre his entire life. In fact, he wouldn’t even match up to an ordinary person since he didn’t have a Dantian. Without using the Nine Star Hegemon Body Art, his only fate would be to sink down to become a weak person that would constantly be taken advantage of.

It took him four hours to fully absorb this FengFu Pill. His FengFu Star’s embryonic form had increased slightly in size, allowing him to control a greater amount of spiritual energy.

By now, it was already the middle of the night. Long Chen stealthily left his room and entered the firewood room. Taking a deep breath, he began to slowly train in the Spirit of the Bull. Long Chen was already completely familiar with his meridians due to those Pill Sovereign memories, so this low grade Battle Skill was something he could master immediately without even the slightest problem.

He walked over to a stone grinder that weighed over half a ton and was normally used to crush up rice crops.

Holding it with both hands, he lifted.

“RISE!”

The huge stone grinder rose into the air, and Long Chen’s impression was that he still had some leftover strength. Nowadays, his strength should be enough to lift around 750 kilograms worth of weight.

However, his strength when Zhou Yaoyang had beaten him had only been 75 kilograms. Compared to before, it was a dramatic ten times increase.

“Excellent, not including other factors and just by relying on my current body strength, I can probably match up to people at the fifth Heavenstage of Qi Condensation.”

Long Chen couldn’t help but feel somewhat excited, and at the same time, he looked even more forward to training in the Nine Star Hegemon Body Art. Right now, he had only condensed an embryonic form, and his power had already increased by such an enormous amount; if he were to truly condense the complete FengFu Star, then just what kind of level would his power rise to?

Hesitating for a while, Long Chen couldn’t resist the urge to continue testing. Setting himself up, the air near his foot started to slowly fluctuate, and a scorching power swept from his foot and through his meridians, slowly collecting into his fist.

Fist of the Bull!

BANG!

Long Chen’s fist smashed onto the stone grinder, and with an explosive bang, the stone grinder was forced into the air and firmly slammed into the wall, causing the entire wall to break down.

Long Chen couldn’t help but foolishly stare at the powerful force. Originally, he had just wanted to experiment a bit with the power; he hadn’t expected that it would cause such a huge disturbance.

From outside the room, other people were all awoken and alarmed. Knowing that he had caused a huge disturbance, he quickly slipped back into his room and laid down to sleep.

However, he was simply too excited to sleep, almost to the point of wanting to dance for joy.

Nine Star Hegemon Body Art… Just what level had this cultivation technique reached? If all nine stars were condensed, then just what kind of power would be produced?

Long Chen was simply too excited and ended up being unable to fall asleep the whole night. When the first glimmer of the sun’s rising lit up his room, he slowly opened his eyes.

“Hehe, you want to take parts of my body? That’s quite a big dream; too bad you’re not able to achieve it.”

After rising, and washing his face, he heard that the servants were still discussing what had happened last night in the firewood room. Welcoming the rising sun, Long Chen couldn’t stop a certain thought from emerging from his heart:

“Today’s a good day. I can accomplish anything.”

Chapter 8 Life and Death Battle

Quite a few people had already assembled around the martial arena. Other than some idle people who regularly enjoyed watching, there were also a few of the imperial capital’s noble heirs.

Today was the day of Long Chen and Li Hao’s life and death battle. Although this place would normally see a constant stream of duels and fights, life and death battles were still very few in number.

What was even odder about this situation was that despite the fact that the two noble heirs who were fighting didn’t have any remarkable cultivation bases, countless people had still come to watch.

In addition, the Youlan Gambling Hall, the most famous gambler in the entire imperial capital, had also come to open up a public betting pool.

Li Hao’s victory: 2 times the odds.

Long Chen’s victory: 10 times the odds.

Since no kinds of counterfeit could occur during a life and death battle, and adding their high statuses as noble heirs, betting on the outcome was extremely exciting to many people.

Even some people who weren’t gamblers also started to place bets, but for the most part, everyone bet on Li Hao’s victory.

Although Long Chen did defeat Li Hao last time, at that time, Li Hao was completely off-guard, and Long Chen had taken advantage of that opening. Such a miracle would not occur a second time.

Only an extremely small portion of people, who liked to either mess around or were desperate, decided to take a long shot and bet on Long Chen.

The betting place was located not far from the martial arena, and the section to bet on Li Hao’s victory was completely packed with people, whereas the section to bet on Long Chen was completely deserted.

“300,000 gold coins on Long Chen.”

Suddenly, a large and lofty man appeared and tossed a crystal card over to the person in charge of the betting.

“What?!”

The handler was completely shocked by this amount; throughout the entire morning, he had only collected ten thousand gold coins up to now. Hearing this new bet, he almost didn’t believe his own ears.

That huge figure was, of course, Shi Feng. He had been entrusted by Long Chen to put all of his gold coins onto his own victory.

Because of his status, Long Chen already knew that the Youlan Gambling Hall would definitely open up a betting pool, and so he had already preemptively told Shi Feng to bet on him.

Even if the Youlan Gambling Hall ended up in a deficit from opening up the betting pool, he definitely wouldn’t back out.

Most of the money he normally earned was from his own personal bets, and as for these outer public bets, he didn’t actually make much money off them. The main reason he had to hold public bets was to keep the people satisfied.

And even if he were to take a loss, with the Youlan Gambling Hall’s imposing wealth, it could easily be brushed off. It was for these reasons that Long Chen decided to join the betting.

Originally, he had planned on just betting with Li Hao, but now he could get ten times the profit by betting with the Youlan Gambling Hall. Long Chen wasn’t an idiot, so of course he knew which was better.

Yesterday, with the help of fatty Yu and his friends, he had collected over two hundred thousand gold coins. When he had handed it over to Shi Feng, Shi Feng had seen how assured Long Chen was acting. Clenching his teeth, he increased the amount to three hundred thousand.

Shi Feng’s family was actually not very rich, mostly because they had a tendency to be rather hot-tempered and were not that good at handling business. The families of fatty Yu and the others tended to be better off.

In order to collect this much money, he had actually used all of his weapons and armor as additional collateral.

All of this was just for Long Chen’s wild and crazy bet. Shi Feng couldn’t hold back having his heart leap a couple of times in nervousness. Brother Chen, you have to stay calm and steady… all your brother’s belongings have all been put on the line.

Li Hao arrived just before noon. With a light push on the ground, he jumped several meters into the air to land on top of the martial arena, arousing a burst of cheers.

However, this time the cheers weren’t for his appearance, but rather because everyone was excited to see the start of a good show.

Today, Li Hao was wearing clean and neat robes that were quite attractive, and a proud thought arose in his mind: Long Chen, the humiliation you’ve given me will be returned to you tenfold!

But even after quite a while passed after Li Hao went onto the stage, no one saw Long Chen appear. No one understood why he hadn’t appeared, and some people began to wonder if perhaps he had chickened out.

Just as everyone was wondering what was going on, an old man in charge of the martial arena coldly told Li Hao, “Your appointment for your battle is for 12:45, so you’re early by almost an hour. You can either continue to wait on top of the stage or you can come off to wait.”

Everyone booed in disappointment when they heard this, and the originally full of vigor Li Hao also became a bit dumbstruck as he had forgotten to check the time.

“Whatever, I’ll just wait for him on the stage. In any case, he’s a person who’s about to die, so his remaining time is more valuable than mine.”

Li Hao indifferently smiled, and just like that, he sat down cross-legged on top of the martial arena, putting on the air of an expert. However, his attempt to maintain an expert’s manner only lasted for a short while before becoming a bit strange…

Because it was noon, the sun was extremely powerful, and to make it worse, the martial arena was topped with black stone tiles, and by now, it was already boiling to the point where it could fry an egg.

Since Li Hao had already sat down, he couldn’t stand back up or it would ruin his act. Therefore, all he could do was suffer.

Of course, some sharp-eyed people had noticed that Li Hao’s bottom had already begun smoking slightly, and in just a moment, it became very obvious and the crowd’s expression became very strange.

“This guy is such an idiot; is he trying to save face? The fight hasn’t even begun, and his butt is already burning,” a maiden gently laughed. In the distance, two veiled women were indifferently looking at the martial arena.

“Speaking frankly, he’s just a phony,” responded the other maiden, shaking her head.

“Sister Meng Qi, we’ve already been here for several days. When do you plan on withdrawing from the marriage agreement?” asked the other one.

The maiden who had been called Meng Qi elegantly creased her brows and somewhat awkwardly said, “Currently, he’s in a very difficult predicament, and if I were to bring up withdrawing from the marriage to him at this time, then it would be too cruel. Even I don’t know what I should do.”

“But delaying this matter isn’t a solution. Master has already urged us several times. If we don’t return to the mountain soon, then we’ll probably be punished. Furthermore, with big sister’s talent, you’ll definitely reach Xiantian and be able to touch the Heavenly Daos. The two of you will be in completely different worlds; there’s no way for you to work it out,” sighed the other maiden.

“But I still feel that doing it in such a manner is still extremely unfair to him… sigh, let’s just watch a bit more.” Meng Qi lightly shook her head, distress appearing within her beautiful eyes.

As Meng Qi hesitated, they saw a disturbance within the distant crowd. Turning to stare, they saw a young man in black robes with sword-like eyebrows and bright eyes slowly walk up. His body seemed to have a unique aura, giving people a very profound feeling.

He appeared just like a well; on the surface, he appeared like nothing was out of the ordinary, but it was impossible to see through him. No one could manage to see through his depths, and his existence appeared like a mystery to them.

Even Meng Qi and the other maiden couldn’t help but feel some fluttering in their hearts when they saw him. Compared to the Long Chen they had seen just a few days ago, it was like the difference between heaven and earth. The current him appeared to be full of self-confidence.

Seeing Long Chen’s arrival, Li Hao jumped up, feeling a burst of scorching pain from his bottom.

Blaming Long Chen, his anger rose even more, and he angrily shouted, “Long Chen, come up and die!”

Long Chen didn’t even spare a glance for Li Hao, and instead, he scanned the crowd and met Shi Feng’s gaze. Shi Feng gave Long Chen a slight nod.

Not only did he see Shi Feng, but he also saw fatty Yu and the others who had apparently come to cheer him on.

Long Chen smiled over to them before turning to walk onto the martial arena. Li Hao had jumped up to show off his skill, but Long Chen decided to simply walk up…

For the moment, the people who had bet on Long Chen’s victory all felt that the money they had gambled was about to be lost forever.

“Long Chen!” Seeing Long Chen walk up, these two words were angrily forced out of Li Hao’s clenched teeth.

“Idiot, your butt’s scorched, isn’t it?” Long Chen sneered at Li Hao.

Actually, he had long since arrived; he merely stayed in the shade further away, and no one had noticed him. However, he had seen very clearly what had been going on on the stage.

“12:45 has arrived; both parties must sign the life and death contract.”

At this moment, the old man took out a document, and Long Chen indifferently smiled and signed his name on top of it.

This time was different from the last duel; conceding to the victor would have no effect this time. The loser’s life and death were held within the victor’s hands.

Li Hao also signed, and with a sinister expression, he said, “You little bastard, today I will return all the humiliation you gave me a hundredfold!”

Now that the life and death contract had been signed, there was no more need for a referee. The current martial arena had now become the ground upon which they would decide who would die today.

“Looks like you don’t understand. You’ve come to provoke me so many times, and I’m not enduring any longer.”

Long Chen took a deep breath… an extremely dense killing intent appeared within his eyes. Ever since Zhou Yaoyang had first said that he wasn’t Long Tianxiao’s son, many people had started using the same kind of insult against him.

“Go to hell you son of a bitch!”

Li Hao sneered, and with a loud bellow, his whole body’s spiritual qi started to circulate, and the spiritual energy visible to the naked eyes could be seen fluctuating around his body.

Everyone in the watching crowd nodded when they saw this. Last time, Li Hao had been extremely unlucky; he hadn’t made any preparations to protect his body, and Long Chen had used one quick attack to beat him. But this time, he had properly prepared and set up his defenses.

Although this was only the spiritual energy of Qi Condensation and had no way of leaving the body, circulating spiritual energy within the body for protection meant that an ordinary person would have a very hard time inflicting any injuries.

After Li Hao had set up his defenses, a sinister smile appeared on his face. He charged towards Long Chen, both hands turning into claws aimed towards Long Chen’s shoulders.

These two claws of his were filled with spiritual qi, making them no different from iron fangs. If ordinary people were to be hit by them, their shoulders would immediately break.

“Good! Li Hao, completely cripple this son of a bitch!” From below the arena, a loud shout came from the person who Long Chen had sent flying within the Imperial College, Wang Mang.

Wang Mang had now already lost half of his teeth while still a youth. And as for any bone-growing medicinal pills, those were far too expensive for his family to buy. Nowadays, he was already full of hatred for Long Chen and seeing Long Chen about to be assaulted, he couldn’t hold back from cheering.

But Shi Feng, fatty Yu, and the others all became extremely worried. From the very start, Long Chen had not shown even the slightest cultivation base, causing their hearts to momentarily get stuck in their throats.

Long Chen coldly smiled as he looked at Li Hao. Taking one step, his whole body turned into a blur as he charged forward towards Li Hao.

BANG!